<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>VertexDezign and Slivicon</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>RealClock Mod</en>
        <de>Echte Uhrzeit Mod</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[Shows the current real time in the upper right corner.

This script creates a configuration xml at first startup in your modSettings folder. There you can adjust the following:
* Position <position isDynamic="bool" x="[0,1]" y="[0,1]"/>
* isDynamic
true: automatically position the text below the game clock, ignore x and y
false: Use x and y ignoring text dimension
* x, y: the position on the screen, see small illustration below for details
1,0 .. 1,1
0,0 .. 1,0
* Color and size of text <rendering color="black|white|r,g,b,a" fontSize="[0,1]"/>
* color: supports the following text values: black, white and all rgba colors seperated by comma in the range [0..1] example king blue "0.25,0.41,0.88,1"
* fontSize: the size of the font to display, a value in the range [0..1], default 0.015. UI Scale is used for calculating the font size to display
* Format of datetime string (see list below)

Position and font size can now also be set with console commands, this makes it a lot easier to position the clock at the wanted position
* vdRealClockPrintCurrentValues -> Shows the current values which are used
* vdRealClockSetPosition 0.9 0.9 -> Set the position, applies immediately
* vdRealClockSetFontSize 0.013 -> Set the font size, applies immediately
* vdRealClockResetToDefault -> Set the values back to their defaults
* vdRealClockSaveSettings -> Saves the changed values in the xml within the modSettings folder

Possible Formats:
%a abbreviated weekday name (e.g., Wed)
%A full weekday name (e.g., Wednesday)
%b abbreviated month name (e.g., Sep)
%B full month name (e.g., September)
%c date and time (e.g., 09/16/98 23:48:10)
%d day of the month (16) [01-31]
%H hour, using a 24-hour clock (23) [00-23]
%I hour, using a 12-hour clock (11) [01-12]
%M minute (48) [00-59]
%m month (09) [01-12]
%p either "am" or "pm" (pm)
%S second (10) [00-61]
%w weekday (3) [0-6 = Sunday-Saturday]
%x date (e.g., 09/16/98)
%X time (e.g., 23:48:10)
%Y full year (1998)
%y two-digit year (98) [00-99]
%% the character `%´

GitHub link: https://github.com/VertexDezign/RealClock
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Zeigt die aktuelle echte Uhrzeit oben rechts im Spiel an.

Das Script erstellt beim ersten Start eine xml Datei im modSettings Ordner. Dort könnt ihr folgende dinge anpassen:
* Position <position isDynamic="bool" x="[0,1]" y="[0,1]"/>
* isDynamic
true: automatische positionierung direkt unter der Ingame Uhrzeit. X und Y werden ignoriert.
false: Nutze x und y, Text Höhe und Breite werden ignoriert
* x, y: Die Position auf dem Bildschirm, welche Ecken welche werte haben könnt ihr der Illustration unten entnehmen.
1,0 .. 1,1
0,0 .. 1,0
* Farbe und Grösse vom Text <rendering color="black|white|r,g,b,a" fontSize="[0,1]"/>
* color: Unterstützt die folgenden beiden Text Werte: black, white und rgba Farben getrennt durch ein Komma im Bereich [0..1] Beispiel Königsblau "0.25,0.41,0.88,1"
* fontSize: Die grösse der Schrift, ein wert im Bereich [0..1], Standard ist 0.015. UI Skalierung wird mit einbezogen bei der Darstellung!
* Format des Strings (siehe Liste unten)

Position wie auch Schriftgrösse können auch über Konsolen Kommandos gesetzt werden, dies vereinfacht das Positionieren an gewünschter Stelle erheblich
* vdRealClockPrintCurrentValues -> Zeigt die aktuellen Werte
* vdRealClockSetPosition 0.9 0.9 -> Setzt die Position auf die gewünschten Werte, sofort sichtbar
* vdRealClockSetFontSize 0.013 -> Setzt die Schriftgrösse auf den angegebenen Wert, sofort sichtbar
* vdRealClockResetToDefault -> Setzt die Werte wieder auf Ihren Standartwert zurück
* vdRealClockSaveSettings -> Speichert die geänderten Daten in der xml im modSettings Ordner

Mögliche Formate
%a Wochentag abgekürzt (z.B., Wed)
%A Wochentag ausgeschrieben (z.B., Wednesday)
%b Monat abgekürzt (z.B., Sep)
%B Monat ausgeschrieben (z.B., September)
%c Tag und Zeit (z.B., 09/16/98 23:48:10)
%d Tag des monats (16) [01-31]
%H Stunde, 24h modus (23) [00-23]
%I Stunde, 12h modus (11) [01-12]
%M Minute (48) [00-59]
%m Monat (09) [01-12]
%p entweder "am" oder "pm" (pm)
%S Sekunde (10) [00-61]
%w Wochentag (3) [0-6 = Sunday-Saturday]
%x Datum (e.g., 09/16/98)
%X Zeit (e.g., 23:48:10)
%Y volles Jahr (1998)
%y zweistelliges Jahr (98) [00-99]
%% das Zeichen `%´

GitHub-Link: https://github.com/VertexDezign/RealClock
]]>
        </de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>store_clock.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="GrisuDebug.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="RealClock.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
